As you can see I have progressed to HR4.
But quests are not cleared and Urgent does not show up.
To fix it we will use FlagCalc tool. Link in description.
In HR1 there are 3 quests so I enter 3.
Check box if you have next HR unlocked.
In HR2 there are 4 quests.
So type in 4.
Check box.
I will repeat it for every HR tab untill i reach the end.
I don't check the box in HR4, because HR5 isn't unlocked
Press Calculate.
Use one of buttons under. I'll use second for Chakratos Manager.
Just in case I will quit the game.
Paste result here and click floppy icon (save).
Starting game again to see if it works.
Greeted by wall of text.
It's a good sign.
And here it is. My Urgent for HR5.
Quests are cleared to the point I have set in calc.
That's it. Hope it will help you.